<contentList>
	<content contentuid="ha1f92690g2af6g4515g9ad4gecd66178217e">Dragon Slayer</content>
	<content contentuid="hf4441e4cgfd32g49bfga758gb0f711be47e8">A former marksman from a long-forgotten regiment, tasked with destroying dragonkind. With their unyielding strength, Dragon Slayers utilize Greatbows to pierce their enemies with arrows the size of spears</content>
	<content contentuid="h6707c781gad82g4884g882bgf27e1cef07de">Dragon Slayers were an elite military unit in Rivellon. Training to become a dragon slayer started at a very young age, and not many endured long enough to become a slayer. The Order of the Dragon Slayers were created by vengeful knights that wanted justice for the death of the Divine at the hands of a dragon knight. In the past, the dragon slayers quickly went from a small band of knights to a mighty army of elites. Today, it is presumed the order was dissolved by Lucian after he was saved by the last Dragon Knight.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5006a424g3d59g4356-baa7g26110b276aab">Runic Knight</content>
	<content contentuid="h71d19b56gda1eg434aga7f0g58ffec6c6a0a">Adept mages who train in the ways of the sword, using special 'Runeblades' as a conduit to enhance their magic. Crafty use of the runes etched upon their blades allow Runic Knights to weave their attacks and spells together, devastating the battlefield</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb07f0fbg0890g42ecg912eg022f0ace33e6">Runic Knights are mages who train in both the ways of the sword and spell, utilizing special 'Runeblades' as a conduit to enhance their magic. Crafty use of the runes etched upon their blades allow Runic Knights to weave their attacks and spells together, devastating the battlefield.</content>
	<content contentuid="h55c685d3g6f64g4e20ga159ga2177754a3da">Chaos Weaver</content>
	<content contentuid="h0e0b0e72ga192g4301gb445g10c5344ab3e3">Sorcerors who wield the power of Chaos, leveraging luck and foresight to lay waste upon the battlefield</content>
	<content contentuid="h33cae2adgffdcg4de5g8a3agb1530c82d79b">Sorcerors who wield the power of Chaos, leveraging luck and foresight to lay waste upon the battlefield.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9045efcdg0e97g4884g95a2g9bfc844868f2">Monk (Quarterstaff)</content>
	<content contentuid="h060a6bb2g4db6g48bag9602g2a9d7c28a85a">Disciplined warriors who wield quarterstaffs, overwhelming enemies with finesse and sheer force of will</content>
	<content contentuid="hc3e23e57gd92dg4aa8ga314gb5a16d81235d">Disciplined warriors who wield quarterstaffs, overwhelming enemies with finesse and sheer force of will.</content>
	<!-- Charges UI text
	<content contentuid="h7da39b62gdaedg4565gbe58gc2e702a725ee">Mastery</content>
	<content contentuid="hd5f94f7eg6557g45cdg835ege011e66a3a3a">Mastery 0/100</content>
	!-->
</contentList>